

wangivy1108@gmail.com

User Experience & Interface Designer

https://ivywang1108.github.io/ivyportfolio/

About:

Hello, I am ready to design something amazing! I love to learn from research, and craft meaningful decisions into useful solutions. I feel proud being able to bring helpful products to people and see their smiles.

Highlights:

Software & Tools: Figma, Adobe Suite, Sketch, Canva, Unity, HTML + CSS. Design Skills: Design Thinking, User Research, Rapid Design, User Testing, Wireframing, Interface Design, Interaction Design, Videography. Soft Skills: Collaboration, Fast Learning, Rapid Thinking, Task Management, Problem Solving, Critical Thinking, Fluent in English and Mandarin.

Experiences:

UX/UI Designer - AutoMetrics

September 2021 - March 2022

- Took ownership of the entire design process, redesigned the user interface of a product that monitors
 welding operation quality, made decisions on the core features and provided users with brand new
 user-friendly and reliable monitor experience.
- Conducted user research to understand current user pain points, developed new product goals and design directions based on user feedback and did competitive analysis to understand industry trends.
- Created marketing videos and brochures that highlighted the company's core features and main services. Also updated the company's website with new product design following the company's brand guideline.

Graphic/UX Design Volunteer - Build a Biz Kids

February 2021 - April 2022

- Maintained the company brand style, designed multiple-day curricula for facilitators that were easy-to-follow, which later became a template for future courses.
- Worked with a company(YouMoveMe) to redesign their Franchise Opportunity Webpage.
- Worked with another designer to re-design the company founder's personal webpage which became more engaging and organised.
- Designed logo for the company's stock game for kids. Did Sketches, and iterations following company brand style while keeping kids as users in mind.

Education:

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Arts - Interactive Arts and Technology

Concentration in Design

September 2015 - December 2020

What I do in my spare time...

Photography, Victuals, Travel, Movies, Lego